{
    "id": "f2054edce1214db38eb54032068da241",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is not ………………. clever as his brother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "more"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1570c65ef6b642e3ac6fe870ec1d203b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He must be punished ………………. he is guilty.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c392b568a1fa42cea6d35aef5dd426a9"
        },
        {
            "question": "A fool …………… his money are soon parted.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "and",
                "as well as"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4c93f12c70224950b85bb092f19777a4"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was not punished …………….. he was guilty.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "as though",
                "as if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e90bf361844b46f18127410e7ae76241"
        },
        {
            "question": "He worked hard ……………… he might pass the examination.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "that",
                "hence"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9c4aedb186ef4e9b86bf4a3ad7f78114"
        },
        {
            "question": "Give every man thy ear, ……………… few thy voice.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "but"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d000f5ee3b2247bb86e3fd89e357bb1b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I waited for him ………………… the clock struck seven.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "unless",
                "up to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "45bca26c333f4dbc9401f745fe7d9429"
        },
        {
            "question": "You will not get the prize ……………… you deserve it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "whether",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3aa3a653116b421dae8e0289f258b528"
        },
        {
            "question": "It has been a year ……………… I saw him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7337d0acc20247749a0359a223aeba90"
        },
        {
            "question": "Hardly had he reached the platform ……………….. the train arrived.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4e5744e8be794d148d6369be1fe031e7"
        },
        {
            "question": "No sooner did he see the tiger ………………. he fainted.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "then",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f29e5969cfdc4e82b3c343b0c429ef74"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. you do not apologize, I shall punish you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "963aa215d8624401a0eabd49cec60ee1"
        }
    ]
}